Downloaded @ subs4free.club
♪ Illumination... ♪
♪ Illumination ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ Illumination ♪
♪ Illumination... ♪
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
♪ Let's go crazy ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Let's go crazy,
let's go crazy ♪
♪ If you don't like ♪
♪ The world you're living in ♪
♪ Take a look around ♪
♪ At least you got friends ♪
♪ You see,
I called my old lady ♪
♪ For a friendly word ♪
♪ She picked up the phone,
dropped it on the floor ♪
♪ "Ah-ah" is all I heard ♪
♪ Are we gonna let
the elevator bring us down? ♪
♪ Oh, no, let's go ♪
♪ Let's go crazy ♪
♪ Let's get nuts ♪
♪ Let's look for
the purple banana ♪
♪ Till they put us
in the truck ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ We're all excited ♪
- ♪ Don't know why ♪
♪ Maybe it's 'cause ♪
♪ We're all gonna die ♪
♪ When we do ♪
- ♪ What's it all for? ♪
♪ You better live now
before the grim reaper comes ♪
♪ Knocking on your door,
tell me ♪
♪ Are we gonna let
the elevator bring us down? ♪
♪ Oh, no, let's go ♪
- ♪ Let's go crazy ♪
- ♪ Let's get nuts ♪
♪ Let's look for
the purple banana ♪
♪ Till they put us
in the truck, let's go! ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ Let's get nuts ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Are we gonna let
the elevator bring us down ♪
♪ Oh, no, let's go ♪
- ♪ Let's go crazy ♪
- ♪ Let's get nuts ♪
♪ Let's look for
the purple banana ♪
♪ Till they put us
in the truck ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Dr. Everything'll
Be All Right ♪
♪ Will make everything
go wrong ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
What's going on?
No time to explain. Run away.
Oh, hey, Sammy.
You really got those moves
locked down now, hmm?
I sure do, Mr. Moon.
Yeah, look at you.
Great job, everybody. Great job.
- Thanks, Mr. Moon.
- Yeah!
I think we pretty much
nailed it.
So, is she here?
There. See the dog,
middle third row?
Oh, she's younger
than I imagined.
Yeah, well, supposedly,
she's the best scout
in show business.
I can't tell
if-if she's enjoying it.
Come on, let's get
a better view.
♪ This I know ♪
♪ He told me,
"Don't worry about it" ♪
"Don't worry no more" ♪
♪ We both know we can't go... ♪
And how we doing
over here, Miss Crawly?
Oh, very good, Mr. Moon.
So far, I counted nine smiles,
two belly laughs
and five chuckles.
Uh, though the last one
could've just been gas.
Well, that's proof, right?
She must like the show.
- Oh, my gosh. You think so?
- I hope so.
All right, now,
keep up the good work.
Come on, everybody,
back to positions.
She'd be, like,
cuckoo not to love the show.
Dream big dreams.
That's what
I always said, right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, looks like we're about
to take this show
to the entertainment capital
of the world.
Mr. Moon, she's leaving.
- Huh?
- She's leaving the show.
♪ He told me,
"You'll never..." ♪
Miss Crawly, stay right here.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna follow that dog.
- ♪ Whoo! ♪
- ♪ I can't feel my face ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ I can't feel my face,
yeah... ♪
Good heavens!
- Hey, Nana.
- What are you doing?
The scout is leaving.
♪ I can't feel my face... ♪
Ah, so she is.
Hurry.
Uh, Suki? Suki Lane?
I'm Buster Moon.
Uh, hi.
So glad you could make it.
Um, would you like some popcorn?
Oh, no, thanks.
I'm not staying
for the second half, so...
Oh. But, uh, we thought
you were enjoying it.
I mean, not that we were
watching you or anything.
It really is a cute little show.
Just not what we're looking for.
But-but wait.
Y-You got to see the second act.
I'm-I'm telling you,
it's a smash.
Okay, Mr. Moon, can I be honest?
- Of course.
- Are you sure?
'Cause folks say that
when they don't really mean it.
No, please, please,
be as honest as you like.
You're not good enough.
What?
Taxi!
You know, maybe I will
have that popcorn.
Look, you've got a nice
little local theater here,
and it's great for what it is,
but trust me, you'd never
make it in the big leagues.
Bye, now.
Well, what did she say?
I'll be right back.
Nah. Mm-mm.
A few laughs,
bunch of quirky ideas.
But, anyway, about Thursday...
Oh, my...
Yeah, hi. It's me again.
Whoa.
- Whoa.
- I'll call you back.
Are you out of your mind?
When are you holding auditions?
Tomorrow.
But there is no way you'll...
Uh, listen, it...
Get out of the road, you idiot!
Hey, do you mind?
I'm in a meeting here.
Could-could you at least
give us a chance
to try out for your boss?
Driver, could you please
lose this maniac?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
No, no, no, no!
♪ When are you
gonna come down? ♪
♪ When are you going to land? ♪
♪ I should have stayed
on the farm ♪
♪ I should have listened
to my old man ♪
♪ You know you can't
hold me forever ♪
♪ I didn't sign up with you ♪
♪ I'm not a present
for your friends to open ♪
♪ This boy's too young
to be singing ♪
♪ The blues ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
Mr. Moon?
♪ So goodbye,
yellow brick road ♪
♪ Where the dogs
of society howl ♪
♪ You can't plant me
in your penthouse ♪
♪ I'm going back to my plow ♪
♪ Back to the howling old owl
in the woods ♪
♪ Hunting
the horny-back toad... ♪
Oh, for heaven's sake.
What can I say, Nana?
- I'm a failure.
- Oh, poppycock.
I was reaching too high.
Honestly, one negative comment,
and it's all, "Woe is me."
Nana, come on.
She said I'm not good enough.
I mean, heck,
I've just been told
that my destiny,
all of my hopes and dreams,
uh, they all end right here.
Well, what did you expect?
That she would drop to her knees
and declare you a genius?
Roll out the red carpet
for the great Buster Moon!
She-she ran me off the road
into a canal.
Well, you're still
in one piece, aren't you?
Well, yeah, but...
Well, anyone who dares set out
to follow their dreams
is bound to face a lot worse
than a dip in the canal.
Ah, Hobbs. I found him.
Uh, bring the car round,
will you?
- There's a good chap.
- I-I...
I just thought she'd at least
see we deserved a shot.
Never mind what this person
you don't even know said.
Do you think you're good enough?
- Of course, but...
- Then you must fight
for what you believe in.
Guts, stamina, faith.
These are the things
you need now,
and without them...
Well, maybe that scout
was right.
Maybe you're not good enough.
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
Oh, I... No, I know, Rosita,
but trust me on this.
It'll be totally worth it.
And listen,
I'm outside her place now,
so can you call the others
and have 'em meet up
in half an hour?
Great. Thank you.
♪ Off, off with your head ♪
♪ Dance, dance
till you're dead ♪
- ♪ Heads will roll ♪
♪ Heads will roll ♪
♪ On the floor ♪
♪ Off, off, off with your head ♪
♪ Dance, dance ♪
♪ Dance till you're dead, dead ♪
♪ Off, off, off with your head ♪
♪ Dance, dance, dance
till you're dead. ♪
Thank you so much.
Good night.
Moon. Hey.
Wow. You were great out there.
I got to go back out
for an encore.
Okay.
Hey, but what are you doing
- after the show?
- Uh, nothing.
Well, listen, I know this is
crazy short notice,
but you always said
you'd come back to work with us
- when the time was right.
- Of course.
Well, this is that time.
Here, paycheck.
I'm getting the gang together
to go audition
- for this huge show...
- Just-just a second.
Hey, Rick, how come
you're only paying me
half what the other acts get?
I pay what I think
you're worth, sweetheart.
Oh, okay. See, I have this rule
about not letting guys like you
tell me what I'm worth,
so, you know, unless I get paid
like everyone else,
I'm out of here.
This is the only club in town.
Where else you gonna play?
I have no idea,
but I'm sure as heck
not sticking around here.
Let's go.
Ooh!
Whoa, whoa. Wait a minute.
You-you got to do the encore.
Hey, Ash!
Deal with it, sweetheart.
Redshore City Bus five
leaving from park 15...
Okay, I got the tickets.
Anyone seen Miss Crawly?
Here you go, Johnny.
- Here's yours, and...
- Mr. Moon.
Uh, uh, I'm sorry,
but I'm really having
second thoughts about this.
What? No, no, no, wait.
All right, last call. Let's go.
- Now, just a second.
- Johnny's right.
I mean, that theater scout,
she didn't think
we were good enough.
- She sounds like a jerk.
- Yeah, total jerk.
Yeah, but she's wrong...
dead wrong.
There's a reason our show
is sold out every night,
and I'm telling you,
her boss is gonna love it.
Ooh. Or maybe
we could just, like,
do a different show, you know?
Gunter, please, I got this.
Seriously, I have this idea
for, like, a space musical.
All right, we're rolling out here.
You don't want to hear
about the space musical?
Guys, come on!
Wait!
Listen, you guys,
I have dreamt of performing
in Redshore City
since I was a little kid.
And besides,
I just convinced my husband
to babysit
for the next 24 hours,
and I am not gonna waste
an opportunity like that.
So come on.
We've got nothing to lose.
Here, Ash.
You come in on page two.
Wait. We're just gonna
rehearse this here
- at the back of the bus?
- Yes, we are.
- Course we are.
- Yep.
We got to get this show
in the best shape ever.
Ah, Miss Crawly,
you made it. Good.
You are an angel, and we're
sure gonna need that...
Whoa!
What the...
Uh, well, you did say,
"Dress to impress."
♪ Time ♪
♪ All the long red lines ♪
♪ That take control ♪
♪ Of all the smoke
like streams ♪
♪ That flow into your dreams ♪
♪ That big blue open sea ♪
♪ That can't be crossed ♪
♪ That can't be climbed ♪
♪ Just born between... ♪
Absolutely right.
Let's just cut that line
and have you just play
the guitar part
through the whole scene.
- Got it.
- Guys, we're here.
All right. Let's go spread
a little Moon Theater magic.
- Woo-hoo!
- Come on!
No.
No? What do you mean, "no"?
For the last time, sir,
no appointment, no entry.
- Um...
- Sir, do I need to call security?
We should go.
Yes, you should. Next, please.
I don't like this.
Hi. How may I help you?
I'm here to see Mr. Crystal
for the presentation.
This is so unfair.
She's, like, totally unfair,
that lady.
I mean, why's she
got to be so snotty about it?
I got all dressed up
for nothing.
Let's just find
somewhere for lunch
- and hang out.
- Everyone, in here.
Quick. Get in.
Hmm.
- Oh, come on.
- So dark in here.
- What's going on?
- Shh! I got to think.
- I've got to think. I've got to think.
- Mr. Moon?
- I've got to think.
- I'm not so good in small spaces.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Ow! Somebody stepped on my trotter.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Okay, honey. Come on.
- Let's get you out of here.
- Aha!
Look at this.
Meena.
Do you think
that's kind of your size?
♪ White shirt now red,
my bloody nose ♪
♪ Sleepin', you're on
your tippy-toes ♪
♪ Creepin' around
like no one knows ♪
♪ Think you're... ♪
Hey, Ricky.
Hi.
Crystal Entertainment.
- Uh, hold one moment, sir.
- Phew.
- I'll-I'll connect you.
- Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Everybody, hold on.
Oh, Mr. Moon?
Hold tight, Miss Crawly.
♪ Make your girlfriend mad
type ♪
♪ Might seduce your dad type ♪
♪ I'm the bad guy ♪
♪ Duh ♪
♪ I like it... ♪
Good job.
Now, into the elevator.
Quick.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Meena! Come on!
♪ I'll let you play the role ♪
♪ I'll be your animal... ♪
We could all get arrested for...
♪ I'm only good at bein' bad ♪
♪ Bad... ♪
Everybody, mop.
Uh...
Where are you going now?
I'm gonna find somewhere
to change out of this stuff.
Ah.
♪ Like a vendetta-ta ♪
♪ I-I-I see how this
is gonna go ♪
♪ Touch me
and you'll never be alone ♪
♪ I-Island breeze
and lights down low ♪
♪ No one has to know ♪
♪ In the middle of the night ♪
♪ In my dreams ♪
♪ You should see
the things we do ♪
♪ Baby, mm ♪
♪ In the middle
of the night... ♪
Look, that's him.
That is the Mr. Crystal.
♪ I know I'm gonna be with you ♪
Garbage.
♪ So I take my time... ♪
- ♪ Hi ♪
- ♪ My name is ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
- ♪ Who? ♪
- ♪ My name is... ♪
♪ Abra-Abracadabra ♪
♪ Abracadabra... ♪
♪ Bangs, she bangs ♪
♪ Oh, baby, when she moves,
she moves... ♪
♪ Hello... ♪
♪ What do you want from me? ♪
♪ Why do you run from me? ♪
♪ What are you wondering? ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ Why are you scared of... ♪
♪ You used to call me
on my cell phone ♪
♪ Late night
when you need my lo... ♪
♪ Talk to me, baby ♪
♪ I'm going blind from this
sweet, sweet craving, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Let's lose our minds
and go crazy, crazy ♪
♪ I-I-I-I-I,
I keep on hopin' we'll eat ♪
♪ Cake by the ocean, uh ♪
♪ Walk for me, baby ♪
♪ I'll be Diddy,
you'll be Naomi, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Let's lose our minds
and go crazy... ♪
Okay, everybody,
if you can leave immediately,
single file,
we'd appreciate that.
Thank you very much.
Jerry, for the love of...
- Sorry, sir.
- Well, where's the next group, Jerry?
Why am I standing here waiting?
How about I...
I just... I just, uh...
Be useful or be gone, okay?
Yes. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Um, okay. Um, you.
Hey. Hey. Yeah, you.
Little guy, you're here
for the audition?
Uh, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yes, we are.
Guys, we're on right now.
- Now?
- What?
Your name?
Hey, your name, please?
Uh, it's Buster Moon
from the New Moon Theater.
And we're very excited to share
our story with you today, sir.
Right, guys?
Yeah, great. Now, get to it.
Of course. Yes.
Okay, guys,
just like we rehearsed.
This is the story
of an ordinary high school girl
who discovers...
Stop.
Stop?
He wants you to stop.
"Ordinary" and "school."
Two words I will never
be associated with.
- Never. Never.
- Where the heck did you
dig these guys up from, huh?
If you could all leave
very quickly,
we'd appreciate that, please.
I need big shows, Jerry.
- Big ideas!
- Yes, sir, big. The biggest.
Hey, I have a big one.
Okay, honey. Come on, let's go.
You know, the sci-fi musical.
- That's big, right?
- Um, uh...
I mean, it's got
the aliens and the robots
and the lasers
and these amazing songs
from, like, Clay Calloway to...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Clay Calloway?
I love Clay Calloway.
I know, right?
I mean, doesn't everybody?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, Jerry?
This is exactly the kind
of big idea I'm talking about.
- Yes, sir.
- So, uh...
so what's the show called?
What's it called? Um...
- Gunter, you, uh...
- you want to...
uh, tell Mr. Crystal
what it's called?
Uh-huh. It's called
Out of This World.
That's right. Just imagine it.
Ash?
Uh, yeah, I got it.
A spectacular musical
that takes your audience
out of this world.
♪ I wanna run ♪
♪ I want to hide ♪
♪ I wanna tear down the walls ♪
♪ That hold me inside ♪
I love this song.
♪ I wanna reach out ♪
♪ And touch the flame ♪
♪ Where the streets
have no name. ♪
Sir, your lunch meeting with...
Oh, my...
Not now.
Moon, how did you get in here?
Hey, he said not now. Psst.
Yeah, I heard him.
Thanks, Jerry.
Are you telling me you-you got
Clay Calloway's permission
to use his song?
- Well, what if I told you I did?
- Ah.
Okay, so what, you got
some kind of personal connection
to this guy?
- How else would I get it?
- Moon!
Wait, if you know him,
then you could get him
in the show, right?
Oh, that'd be huge for me.
Huge.
Sir, I'm sorry, but seriously?
You think this little guy
from nowhere
can get Clay Calloway
in the show?
Well, Suki,
for your information,
I am not just
a little guy from nowhere.
Consider it done, sir.
I'll give you three weeks, Moon.
Three weeks to get this show
up and running, okay?
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Moon, do you really know
Clay Calloway?
Shh, shh. Not now.
- Jerry.
- Oh! Right here, sir.
I want these guys
to start work right away.
Set 'em up with our designers,
our dancers, whatever they need.
And get 'em rooms
at the hotel, okay?
The very best suites.
The whole shaboodle.
Yes, sir. Yes, of course.
Uh, hey, one last thing.
Don't you ever do nothing
to make me look bad.
You got that?
Oh, I will never
let that happen, sir.
You better not,
or I'll throw you off the roof.
Great job, everyone.
Take it away, Raoul.
Oh, my gosh.
- Is this really happening?
- Yeah!
We're playing
Redshore City, baby!
Yes, we are, Gunter.
Gunter, sci-fi musical?
You're a genius.
Yeah, well, Mama always said,
"Gunter, you're not as stupid
as your papa."
No, you're not.
Hey, Suki.
No hard feelings, huh?
You have no idea
what you're getting into.
Whoa.
- Are you out of your mind?
- What?
Clay Calloway?
I'm, like, his biggest fan,
and I can tell you,
the guy is a recluse.
Seriously, after his wife died,
no one's seen him
in over 15 years.
Ah. That's not good.
No, it's not.
Uh...
Miss Crawly, I need you
to help me find Clay Calloway.
An address,
a phone number, anything.
- But we've got to find that guy.
- Yes, sir.
♪ Think about it... ♪
Good morning!
I'm Linda Le Bon, and have I got
some hot news for you.
♪ Down in the heart
or hidden... ♪
Infamous billionaire
Jimmy Crystal has hired
- an unknown theater producer...
- What?
by the name of Buster Moon.
♪ Look inside your heart
and I'll look inside mine ♪
♪ Things look so bad
everywhere ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ In this whole world,
what is fair? ♪
♪ We walk the line
and try to see ♪
♪ Try to see ♪
♪ Falling behind
in what could be ♪
♪ Oh, oh, bring me
a higher love ♪
♪ Bring me a higher love, oh ♪
♪ Bring me a higher love ♪
♪ Where's that higher love
I keep thinking of? ♪
♪ That love, that love ♪
♪ Bring me higher love ♪
♪ Love, that love,
that love... ♪
Okay, so this guy
is coming in from that side,
and it's, like, cuckoo crazy,
and then I think
we should have, like,
this cool alien tango scene.
"Alien tango scene."
Oh. I love it.
Wait. I've got a better idea.
What if it was, like,
a big underwater scene instead?
- Underwater?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm sure of this. Write it down.
- Mm, okay.
- Wait, wait.
Stop your clicky-clacky.
I have a better idea.
Uh, you can't keep
changing your mind.
Why?
Why? Because in
exactly 20 minutes,
the stage crew are coming here
to start work on our show,
and we need to lock
this stuff down.
Oh, my gosh, they're early.
Ooh, and I want to have, like,
this beautiful love scene...
Miss Crawly,
anything on Calloway?
- Hmm, not a thing.
- Oh, geez.
Ah, Mr. Moon.
We're your production team,
and we're here to start...
Yes, yes, yes. Uh, you're here
to work on the show.
And I would gladly invite
you all in right now, but...
We should totally do,
like, a battle scene!
Gunter, no, not now.
I just need a little
more time to, you know,
hammer out a few minor, little
details, so would it be okay
if you all could
come back in, like,
I don't know, an hour?
Or maybe four?
And I really appreciate
your patience.
Thank you so much.
Hmm. Okay.
Okay.
That was not a great start.
- Oh, look, it's a gift from Mr. Crystal.
- Huh.
It-it says, um,
"Don't screw up, Moon, or else."
Ooh, I've got a better idea.
♪ What about the mambo? ♪
♪ And everyone's
in space suits ♪
♪ A great idea, I think so. ♪
Good morning.
May I have everyone's
attention, please?
Thank you. Yes.
Okay, um, on behalf
of myself and the cast,
I just want to say that
to be given
this incredible opportunity
to work with you all here
at the Crystal Tower Theater,
well, it's an honor
for all of us.
And I believe that, together,
we can make a show
that'll take the audience
out of this world.
And a big thanks
to Steve over here
for staying up all night
to make this model.
Great work, Steve.
And here she is, folks.
The star of our show, Rosita.
That's you, baby!
The lead role?
Trust me,
you are perfect for it.
Wait till my kids
hear about this.
And so the story goes like this.
Rosita plays
an astronaut searching
for a missing space explorer.
Together,
with their trusty robot...
- That's me.
- Mm-hmm, yes.
They follow the trail
across four planets.
There's a planet of war,
a planet of love,
a one of despair and one of joy.
And each planet will have its
own spectacular musical number
performed by one of our terrific cast.
A-And how does it end?
Do I find the explorer?
Oh, we have no clue what
we're going to do at the end.
Gunter, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We do have great ideas
for the ending.
We just... All right.
We've only got three weeks
to make this reality, folks.
Let's get to work.
Johnny, you are gonna play
an alien warrior
in a fantastic battle scene.
- Yes!
- Come with me.
Johnny, I want you to meet
your fellow dancers.
- Hello, lads.
- Hey, how you doing?
Uh, wait. You said
mine was a battle scene.
Well, it is, but Gunter saw it
as more of a... a dance battle.
- Yeah!
- Okay...
Johnny, don't worry.
You're gonna be working with
the number one choreographer
in Redshore City.
"Klaus Kickenklober."
Yep. Klaus will turn you
into a pro in no time.
- Okay.
- Uh...
Mr. Moon?
Meena, you okay?
Gunter said I'm in
a romantic scene and, uh, uh...
I have to kiss someone.
Yeah. It's gonna be an amazing,
beautiful, romantic scene.
Mr. Moon, I've never even had
a boyfriend
or any of that stuff.
Ah, don't you worry.
I'm gonna cast
a great partner for you.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Mr. Moon, we're ready
to start building
the rest of the sets and...
Okay, okay, okay, listen.
I don't exactly know
what they are yet,
so could you give me one more
night to figure this out?
Hey, this guy
doesn't have it figured out,
so we can't start work right now.
Mason?
- Did everybody hear that?
- Hey, don't...
He does not have the show
figured out.
I'm looking into his eyes,
- and all I see is fear.
- Uh-uh. Mm-mm.
Hey, hey, hey, listen, listen...
- And a little bit of shame.
- Yeah, yeah.
Look, I-I think
everyone heard you, Mason.
Thank you so much.
Gunter... we have work to do.
And then I'm thinking,
Ash, you know, she can, like,
totally have a duet
with Clay Calloway,
'cause, like, she's a star
that is, like,
guiding them all the way
back home again.
Yes, Gunter.
That's perfect for Ash.
Mommy!
Oh, my darlings, you're here.
Yeah, Johnny!
Oh.
My gosh, I wasn't
expecting you till the morning.
I know, but they couldn't
wait to see you.
The star of the show, huh?
Can you believe it?
It's literally
my dream come true.
- I know. Mwah.
- Ew.
I am so proud of you, honey.
Uh... help.
Mr. Moon, I found him.
- Clay Calloway?
- Yeah. I found his home address.
No way.
Yes way.
Miss Crawly, I'm gonna need you
to go visit him
first thing tomorrow.
- Oh, yes, sir.
- You'll need to rent a car
and take him a letter and, uh,
maybe that fruit basket.
Yes, the fruit basket.
- You got that?
- Got it.
And one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
We're dancing. We're dancing.
We're holding. We're holding.
Stay en pointe.
Shuffle and hold.
I said hold, Johnny.
He's not holding.
- And one, two, three, four...
- All right, I'm... I am trying.
Let's not forget,
this is Redshore City,
not your little local theater.
And five, six, seven, eight.
Ryan, that was excellent.
Johnny, you are doing it wrong.
That was awful.
Come on, Johnny.
You can do better.
- He's freaking me out.
- Johnny.
- I'm trying.
- Thrust.
And thrust, and thrust.
You're not thrusting, Johnny.
- Come on. Thrust.
- Thrust, and thrust.
Still not thrusting.
Can you thrust, please?
Five, six, seven,
and tippy-toes, tippy-toes.
I don't see your tippy-toes.
Oh, come on,
he's having a laugh.
- Tippy-toes. Come on, let's go.
- Seven, and...
That is rubbish,
terribly poor, really bad.
That bloke absolutely hates me.
Hang in there, Johnny.
The first week's always tough.
Yeah. You're right.
You're right.
Meena, come and meet
your partner.
Oh, my gosh, he's here?
Yep. He's called Darius.
Won a ton of awards.
And I think you guys are
gonna have great chemistry.
♪ If I was your boyfriend ♪
♪ I'd never let you go ♪
♪ Keep you on my arm, girl ♪
♪ You'd never be alone ♪
♪ I can be a gentleman ♪
♪ Anything you want ♪
- Wow.
- ♪ If I... ♪
That's really great, Darius.
Uh, yeah, it's a scene
from the last show I was in.
I'm sure you heard of it...
Hope Against Hope.
Gosh, I won every award in town.
Uh, the Golden Piccolo
for Best Crying.
Uh, the Archer Newman Award
for Outstanding Hair.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, my costar,
she was just like you, Gina.
- She was, uh...
- Uh, it's Meena.
Excuse me?
M-My name, it's Meena, not Gina.
Yeah, okay.
In the future,
if you could not interrupt me,
that would be way better.
Okay, okay. Let's rehearse.
♪ Don't wanna close my eyes ♪
♪ Don't wanna fall asleep ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I'd miss you, babe ♪
- Uh, uh, uh...
- ♪ And I ♪
- Oh.
♪ Don't wanna miss a thing... ♪
No, no, no, no, no, uh...
This song is not
helping her at all.
♪ When I saw you in that dress ♪
♪ Looking so beautiful ♪
♪ I don't deserve this ♪
♪ Darling, you look ♪
♪ Perfect tonight. ♪
Oh, boy.
So, where's Calloway?
Uh, he'll be here very soon.
- Mm, is that so?
- It is indeed so.
In fact,
my trusty assistant Miss Crawly
is on her way
to meet him right now.
- ♪ Wake up ♪
- ♪ Grab a brush and put a little makeup ♪
- ♪ Makeup ♪
- ♪ Hide your scars to fade away the shake-up ♪
- ♪ Doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Why'd you leave the keys upon the table? ♪
- ♪ The table ♪
- ♪ Here you go, create another fable ♪
- ♪ You wanted to ♪
♪ Grab a brush and put
a little makeup... ♪
Your
destination is on the right.
On the right. Okay.
Oh.
Mr. Calloway?
Hello?
Is anybody home?
Ooh.
Okay, I got you.
Clay Callowa...
Oopsie-daisy.
Hello.
I can't take your call
right now,
but please leave me a message
after the beep.
Miss Crawly, it's me, Mr. Moon.
I haven't heard from you
in a while.
I'm starting to worry here.
Moon!
Mr. Crystal.
Your set designs are a disgrace.
What?
I'm just messing with you.
Where's your sense of humor,
huh?
Anyway, this is
my daughter Porsha.
Hey.
Nice to meet you, Porsha.
She wants to meet Calloway.
Big fan, aren't you, baby?
Oh, my gosh, I'm, like,
so into vintage right now.
So, where is he?
Uh, well...
I-I'm not expecting Clay
on set just yet.
- I mean...
- Wait.
Is this, like, a sky-fi show?
Uh, sci-fi? Yes. Yes, it is.
Oh, my gosh, I love sky-fi.
Mr. Moon!
- We're ready on the tower.
- Oh.
Thank you, Sasha. We, uh...
We're gonna rehearse,
Mr. Crystal, so...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. You go
and do your rehearsing thing.
- Go, go, go, go.
- Playback.
Okay.
All set.
Just remember to release
the safety catch
before you jump, okay?
Okay, yeah.
Is Mommy gonna jump off that?
She sure is.
Wow!
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Take it ♪
♪ I should've said it before ♪
♪ Tried to hide it ♪
♪ Fake it ♪
♪ I can't pretend anymore... ♪
Uh...
Oh, my gosh.
Gunter.
Mr. Moon,
I think Rosita's having, like,
a major freak-out up here.
Oh, no.
Hey, Moon, you really think
the mommy pig's
gonna pull this off?
Mommy pig?
Absolutely, sir.
Believe me, there's nothing
Rosita can't do.
- I can't do this.
- Why didn't you tell me
- you were afraid of heights?
- I wasn't.
I-I mean, I've never been
afraid in my whole life before,
but I... suddenly, I just...
I don't know
what happened to me.
- Did my kids see that?
- Hey, you guys.
What's going on up here?
Who is that?
Ooh. Can I try?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I-I can't let you jump off here.
Daddy, he won't let me jump!
Moon, come on.
Let her do the thing.
- Yay!
- Porsha, wait!
Whoa, hey. Uh, just a minute.
I love it!
Whee! It's easy!
All right,
let's get you down, Rosita.
Oh, my gosh, you guys.
This is exactly like
the dream I had last night.
Seriously,
you-you were all there.
And you and you and that
funny-looking guy over there.
- Um...
- All of you.
And you asked me
to sing for you.
I... I did?
Yeah. And so, I was like...
♪ This girl is on fire ♪
♪ She's walking on fire ♪
♪ This girl is on fire. ♪
Well, that's a lovely dream
you had there, Porsha.
Um, okay, everybody, back
to first positions, please.
Here, Rosita.
You want to try
with the helmet this time?
Oh, but now I know
what the dream meant.
Yeah. She's afraid.
She'll never be able
to play the part.
But here I am, and I'm young,
and I'm not afraid at all.
I-I can't just give you
Rosita's part. I mean...
Moon, walk with me.
What's wrong with you, huh?
What, you got a kink
in your think?
It's just that I wrote
this part for Rosita and...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me tell you something, Moon.
What you got here is an
opportunity to make me happy.
And when an opportunity
like that comes along,
you'd better grab it!
You get me?
- Uh...
- What?
You don't think my daughter's
good enough for your show?
No, Mr. Crystal.
Well, I-I think she's wonderful.
Oh, good.
So you'll figure it out.
I'll... Yes, I will.
Daddy, I'm hungry
for French toast.
Jerry!
- Yes, sir.
- Get her some French toast.
And, by the way, I like the set.
That whole
"rings moving around" thing.
Creative, quirky. I like it.
Bye, Daddy.
Mm-kay.
Let's have Porsha measured
for a costume
right away, please.
Yes, right away, people.
Would you just get
the French toast, Jerry?
I'm getting
the French toast, Suki.
You okay?
A little shaky, but I'm okay.
Yeah. You know, uh...
Look, maybe this is
for the best, huh?
I mean, you really were
scared up there.
Right.
I'll write you another part,
Rosita.
A really... a really,
really great part.
- You all right?
- Oh, I'm fine.
- Really?
- Yes. You're all very sweet,
but like Mr. Moon says,
this is probably for the best.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
I am completely fine with this.
Hey, honey.
Are you... you-you're sure
you're not, you know, upset?
No, I-I'm good.
Um, can I please just have
the bathroom to myself
- for five minutes?
- You got it.
Okay, kids, go get your jammies on!
Thank you for choosing
to drive with Royalty.
All right. Bye-bye.
♪ Yo, yo, yo, they wanna know ♪
♪ Who's that girl? ♪
♪ Uh, yo, yo,
come on, come on... ♪
Oh, hello, young sir.
Um, oh, yes, you'll...
you'll be pleased to hear
I did bring it back
with a full tank.
And one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
five, six, seven. And...
Sorry I'm late,
Mr. Kickenklober.
I was practicing all morning.
I just lost track of time.
Oh, I thought maybe
you had been involved
in a terrible accident
and we'd never have to
see you again, but never mind.
Seriously?
Why do you have to be
so mean all the time?
'Cause only when we suffer...
can we be great.
Places, everyone!
Ryan, you'll be playing
his opponent
in the climax of the scene.
Now...
let's see if little Johnny
has learned the steps.
Whoa. S-Sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Ow!
- Wrong.
Sorry.
Again!
Higher.
So bad.
Again!
No!
Come on.
Yuck! Again!
- Whoa.
- Come on!
Man.
♪ Hot tamale, hotter
than a Somali, fur coat ♪
♪ Ferrari, hop out the stu',
jump in the coupe ♪
♪ Big Dipper on top
of the roof ♪
♪ Flexing on...
as hard as I can ♪
♪ Eating halal,
driving the Lam' ♪
♪ Told that...
I'm sorry, though ♪
♪ 'Bout my coins like Mario,
yeah, they call me Cardi B ♪
♪ I run this...
like cardio, whoo ♪
♪ I said I like it like, whoo ♪
♪ I said I like it like ♪
Thank you.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Wow, wow.
You are an amazing crowd.
Mate, you're amazing.
Much appreciated.
- Thank you so much.
- Uh...
Uh, um...
Thank you for coming.
Okay. Thank you very much,
little guy.
Wow, so kind.
Listen, could I buy you a coffee
or, uh, maybe something to eat?
Whoa, that's forward, ain't it?
What? No, no, no.
I didn't mean...
I just would love to talk
to you about maybe...
Hey! You got a license to perform here?
Actually, I'd love a chat.
Let's go.
Here you go.
One volcano smoothie
with extra chocolate lava.
Shut up.
Here. 50 bucks.
Honestly, if you could just
give me some dance lessons,
you would literally
be saving my life.
Wait, if you're in a real show,
how come you don't have
a choreographer?
I do, but it turns out
he's a massive weirdo.
And how do I know
that you're not a weirdo?
Hmm? How do I know
that you're legit?
Well, just come with me to
rehearsals. See for yourself.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm not just gonna follow
some guy I don't know
to rehearsals.
Well, how else am I supposed
to prove that I'm legit?
♪ And maybe I should stop
and start confessing ♪
♪ Confessing, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, I've been shaking,
I love it when you go crazy ♪
♪ You take all my inhibitions ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ You take me places
that tear up my reputation ♪
♪ Manipulate my decisions ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
- ♪ Oh-oh ♪
- Yeah! Woo-hoo!
♪ There's nothing
holdin' me back... ♪
I knew you were a weirdo.
♪ There's nothing
holdin' me back. ♪
Whoa.
- This is sick!
- See?
First positions, please.
Whoa. Mate, look at that.
Look at that.
Hey. Who are you?
Ah, it's all right.
She's with me.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Nooshy.
I'm his dance coach.
And I really love that hat.
She's right. Great hat.
You think some riffraff
street dancer
can help you more than me?
- Riffraff?
- Okay, okay. Hang on.
She's just gonna give me
some extra lessons, that's all.
Oh, because I,
Klaus Kickenklober,
master choreographer,
am not good enough for Johnny.
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Yes, I'm irrelevant to him.
I'm just a stupid,
fat, old monkey.
- I don't think that at all.
- I do.
Shh! Please.
She's only trying
to help me, that's all.
Dude, anyway, I only need
two days with him.
Two days? Ha!
200 years, more like.
Two days. He'll be amazing.
Oh, really?
Well, if he is,
I will eat my hat.
Okay, everybody, from the top.
Stand by, playback.
Lots of energy now, and...
Wha...?
Miss Crawly?
You can't go back there,
Mr. Moon.
- Never. Never.
- What? What happened to you?
That lion, you see,
he's crazy. Crazy!
Oh, he's crazy.
Pew. Pew, pew.
- Wow, she's a mess.
- Pew, pew! Pew...
So, you're not gonna
go out there, are you?
Gonna have to. I mean...
All set over here, Mr. Moon.
Okay. Playback!
Stand by, Rosita.
And... action!
♪ Ooh, look what
you made me do ♪
♪ Look what you made me do ♪
♪ Look what you
just made me do ♪
♪ Look what you just made me ♪
♪ Ooh, look what
you made me do ♪
- And cue Porsha.
- ♪ Look what you made me do ♪
♪ Look what you
just made me do ♪
♪ Look what you just
made me, ooh. ♪
Take that, you nasty
alien monster.
Did I do good?
Yeah.
That was so good.
Yay!
Did you hear that?
He thinks I'm awesome.
Okay, she cannot act.
Shh. I know. I know.
But I got to keep
Mr. Crystal happy.
Take that, you nasty
alien monster.
Excuse me, but Mr. Crystal
wants to see you.
Take that,
you nasty alien monster.
Oh. Well, I could come by
this afternoon.
He means now. Right now.
O... kay.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yes, I did. Yes, I did.
- Come on in.
- Whoa.
This place is incredible.
Pretty great, huh?
So, how's it going
with Calloway?
Calloway?
It's, uh... it's good.
- Yeah. Very good.
- Right, right.
Well, let me ask you something.
What did I do to make you
disrespect me, huh?
What?
Oh, what?
You think I'm an idiot?
Some kind of bozo?
No. No, sir, not at all.
My team, they talked
to Calloway's lawyer,
and they say he's never
heard of you or your show.
Really? They said that? Uh...
- You lied to me!
- I-I didn't mean to.
Okay? Honestly, I really
thought I could get him.
No one makes me look
like a fool! No one!
I-I wouldn't dream of doing that to you.
I swear, if you didn't have
my kid in your show,
you'd be out
of that window by now!
Please, please, please.
I-I'm so sorry.
You'd better have Calloway
by the end of next week,
- or so help me!
- I-I-I will.
I-I-I'll get him.
I won't let you down, sir.
Oh, I know
you won't let me down.
- Jerry, get in here!
- Yes, sir. Right here, sir.
- Clean this mess up, will you?
- Yes, absolutely, I'd love to.
Listen up.
I got to go to Calloway's,
and I got to go ASAP.
- Oh, no, please don't go there.
- D-Don't worry. Don't worry.
I know you said he's crazy,
but I'll be all right.
- Oh, can I go with you, please?
- Uh, I don't know.
Come on, you're gonna need me.
I know everything
about this guy.
- Uh... I think you're right.
- Yes!
Now, listen, Gunter,
you've got to figure out
the ending of this show
on your own.
- On my own?
- Yes.
Miss Crawly, I need you
to take charge while I'm away.
- Yes, sir.
- Now, listen to me.
You got to bring
your A game here, Miss Crawly.
I'm serious.
You got to be tough.
- Yes, I got to be tough.
- You got to be firm.
Oh, and I got to be firm. Yes.
And you cannot...
I repeat, cannot...
let production fall behind,
not one little bit.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir, Mr. Moon, sir.
Mason!
That volcano should've been
finished yesterday!
- W-We're on it, Miss Crawly.
- You better be!
Meena, Darius,
take it from the top,
and this time, put a little
juice in it, will you?
I'm trying my best, Miss Crawly.
A little juice?
Hey, everybody.
You're two hours late
for rehearsal!
Wait. Wait, where's the koala?
Who are you?
I'm in charge! That's who!
Now, get your tail to wardrobe,
sweetheart.
Oh, my gosh.
There he is.
That's him.
Holy moly, it really is.
He doesn't look so scary.
Mr. Calloway!
- Go away!
- No, please.
We-we-we just want to talk
to you for one minute.
That's all.
We are not leaving
until you talk to us.
Fine. If you're not
coming over here,
we're coming over to you.
No! Stay off the fence!
Don't listen to him.
Stop, stop, stop!
Porsha, you're still
messing it up.
It's not my fault.
He keeps missing the catch.
I think she's trying to kill me.
Reset. Let's go again.
Meena! Darius!
We're coming to you next,
and I better see
some chemistry between you two.
Okay, let's run these steps
one more time.
So, music starts, I step out,
do my moves, fancy moves.
Step together, drop.
Gazing at each other like
we're burning up with love...
What are you doing
with your face?
Your face looks broken.
What is that?
Uh...
I was falling in love?
Yeah, Gina, listen.
I'm sorry, that-that's not what
falling in love with me
looks like.
I... I should know.
I see it day after day,
week after week.
Let's run it again.
From the top!
And five, six, seven, eight.
And one...
Would you like
some ice cream, ma'am?
Or should I say, Your Majesty?
Uh...
I just...
You look like a goddess,
and, uh...
and-and-and lucky for you,
it's "free ice cream
for all goddesses" day.
Aw.
That's cherry cheesecake,
and I-I make it all myself.
See, my truck's
right over there.
Come by anytime...
Your Majesty.
Ooh, that... Are you okay?
Buster?
You okay?
Ash?
Where are we?
We're in Clay's house.
Oh, my gosh.
- Have you talked to him yet?
- Uh-huh.
- You have?
- We were just discussing
whether he'd consider
being in our show.
What did he say?
He said no.
Not in a million years.
Please, Mr. Calloway.
Look, you don't...
you don't realize how much
it would mean to have
you in our show and...
Will you stop your yakking?
Here.
Your friend left this
on my property.
And I want you gone
in the morning.
And that's why they say,
"Never meet your heroes."
Step, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Yes!
Whoa, mate.
You're not ready
to be busting out these moves.
- Sorry.
- Look at you.
Klaus has thrown you
in the deep end
and drained out
all of your confidence like...
Don't worry.
We'll build up to it
step-by-step.
Just forget what Klaus told you
and go with the flow.
♪ Hey, uh, uh ♪
♪ I'd rather be
nobody other than me ♪
♪ Mark my words,
my talk ain't cheap ♪
♪ Life's a dream,
but I'm not sleep ♪
♪ I, I feel like a work of art ♪
♪ I'm not easily forgot ♪
♪ Had to set myself apart ♪
♪ I'm just following my heart ♪
♪ I'm just following my path ♪
♪ I'm just here
to make it last ♪
♪ I'm not living in the past ♪
♪ If you don't feel me,
kiss my ♪
♪ Uh, uh, suéltate ♪
♪ Uh, uh, suéltate. ♪
Nailed it!
Now, didn't you say
you were gonna eat your hat?
Well, there you go.
Mmm. Yum-yum.
♪ I love it
when you call me señorita ♪
♪ I wish I could pretend
I didn't need ya... ♪
Girl, that is your fourth today.
I know, I know.
But I can't stop.
It's 'cause I really want
to talk to him.
But...
but when I get close,
I get nervous, so...
so I just buy another ice cream.
♪ It felt like
ooh-la-la-la, yeah. ♪
Uh, honestly,
th-this is gonna be
the greatest show
I have ever made.
Whoa!
And when you see
the sets and the...
Turn on that tap for me.
Tap? Uh, sure.
So, anyway...
Whoa!
Oopsie-daisy.
Moon, you okay?
I'm okay!
It's tea.
You drink it.
I promise,
this is going to be
the most wonderful...
I mean, fantastic show ever.
Did you put honey in this?
A-And the ending? Oh, boy.
I mean, i-it's gonna end
with you
and your song...
You don't want to do the show.
Besides,
lost my singing voice, so...
Your voice sounds fine to me.
This...
This is all because
you lost your wife, isn't it?
Okay, porcupine.
We're not talking about my Ruby.
Look, I know she inspired
so many of your songs...
All of my songs.
Right.
I... I can't imagine
what it must be like
to lose someone so special,
but do you think this is what
Ruby would've wanted for you?
I mean, you out here on your own
and never singing again?
No, y-you don't understand.
There's... there's no rock star
living here anymore.
Clay, you just need
to play again.
Your songs will bring you back.
You can.
You can reconnect with...
No, I can't!
I haven't even heard one
of my songs in over 15 years.
And for good reason.
Ruby was everything.
And I don't like honey
in my tea.
He's not gonna change his mind.
He will.
But you should go back.
Me? What about you?
I just need time with him.
I can't just
leave him like this.
Ten-hut!
- Whoa.
- Welcome back, Mr. Moon, sir.
Uh, thank you, Miss Crawly.
Oh, and I have
something for you.
Thank you, Mr. Moon, sir.
All right, you can ease off
the attitude now.
Oh, oh, yes, yes.
So, any luck with Clay Calloway?
Shh! Not yet.
But if anyone can convince him,
it's Ash, so...
All right, folks, tomorrow,
we have our first run-through,
so let's get this show
in shipshape shape.
And cue Porsha.
Captain's log.
I must take care,
for I have landed
on the Planet of War.
Ooh. Okay, so let's just
hold it right there, folks.
Uh, everyone, take five.
What the heck is
a captain's log, anyway?
Um, Porsha, can I have a word?
Porsha, you know I truly believe
that this show, i-it...
it's close to being fantastic,
maybe even perfect.
- Thank you.
- Y-Yeah, yeah,
but-but, see, to make it
the best it can be...
well, I got to make
some changes.
Uh-huh.
Like...
uh...
I have to give the lead role
back to Rosita.
What?
I'm just offering you
the opportunity
- to switch roles with...
- You're firing me?
No, I-I'm not firing you.
Oh, wait till my dad hears
that you fired me.
But I'm not firing you.
Please, wait!
Oh, my gosh.
You all hate me, don't you?
No, no, no, we don't hate you.
We all think you're terrific!
Well, I don't care
if you hate me.
Please stop.
You and your stupid,
stupid sky-fi show
can go to heck!
Porsha, stop. Wait!
Oh, I am one dead koala.
♪ I'm not afraid ♪
♪ Of anything in this world ♪
♪ There's nothing
you can throw at me ♪
♪ That I haven't already heard ♪
♪ I'm just trying to find ♪
♪ A decent melody ♪
♪ A song that I can sing ♪
♪ In my own company ♪
♪ I never thought
you were a fool ♪
♪ But, darling,
look at you, ooh ♪
♪ You gotta stand up straight ♪
♪ And carry your own weight ♪
♪ These tears are going
nowhere, babe ♪
♪ You've got to
get yourself together ♪
♪ You've got stuck in a moment ♪
♪ Now you can't get out of it ♪
♪ Oh, love, look at you now ♪
♪ You got yourself
stuck in a moment ♪
♪ And you can't get out of it. ♪
♪ Hot News. ♪
And the hottest story today:
Porsha Crystal was reportedly
fired from her father's show.
He fired my daughter?
My daughter?
Would you be quiet?
You've embarrassed me enough.
But, Daddy...
Now the whole world thinks I got
a talentless loser
for a daughter.
Take her home.
Bring me Moon.
♪ He will not always say ♪
♪ What you would have him say ♪
♪ But now and then, he'll say ♪
♪ Something wonderful... ♪
Ash? Now is not a good...
Moon, I've got him!
- What?
- I got Calloway!
Here, he wants to talk to you.
Your friend is even
more annoying than you are.
Don't listen to him.
We're heading to Redshore
right now.
- You are?
- Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, this is great news,
seriously.
You may have just
saved my life here.
Okay.
Here we go.
Mr. Moon, what have you done?
Mr. Crystal. Aah!
I got some great news.
Clay Calloway is
on his way here right now.
Everybody, out.
Okay, I think I know what
this might be about, and I...
You fired Porsha.
No. No. I never fired her.
You calling her a liar?
No, no, no, no,
she just got it wrong, is all.
I was only trying to help her
do the best she could,
and be-believe me, I-I-I just
wanted to do the right thing.
The right thing to do...
- is what I tell you to do!
- But I did!
I-I-I delivered a great show.
And Ca-Calloway, he's coming.
No, no, no! Stop! Stop!
No!
You really think
I'd let a lowlife
little amateur loser like you
humiliate me?
Please! Please!
- You made me look bad.
- No, no!
I didn't mean to!
No!
So I'm gonna have to let you go.
What? Whoa!
Sir. Uh, sir, sir, sir.
I'm-I'm so sorry, um,
so sorry to bother you,
but, uh, you have a live
TV appearance in just a moment,
so it-it might be better
if we just
put a pin in this right now.
Um...
You-you nearly killed me.
And I'll finish the job later.
No.
No! No!
Help!
Help! Jerry! Anyone!
No. Help, please!
Shh!
You need to get out of this city
and never, ever come back.
Do you understand? Never.
Okay, okay. I understand.
I told you
you were not cut out for this.
He tried to kill me.
Yeah, and when he finds you're
gone, he'll have his thugs
looking all over for you.
Okay. Thank you, Suki.
I'm so, so...
Get out of here.
Uh, what did you say, Mr. Moon?
Get out! All of you!
Get out of there right now!
There's no time to explain.
Just get the cast
and meet me back at the hotel!
And we're live in five, four,
three, two...
♪ Hot News ♪
- ♪ Hot News... ♪
- Jerry, go get my snacks.
Yes, sir.
What a great show we have...
Here to discuss the drama
- surrounding his new show...
- Sir! Uh, sir, sir, sir.
- Mr. Redshore City himself...
- What?
please welcome
Mr. Jimmy Crystal.
Come on out here, Jimmy.
- Don't make us beg.
- Moon got out.
- Find him.
- Does this guy know
how to make an entrance or what?
Hey, everybody!
Good to see you.
Linda, I got some hot news
for you.
You look terrific.
It is so good to see you.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for having me.
Oh, my gosh.
Billionaire Magazine
Man of the Year
three years in a row,
owner of the largest...
theater chain in the world...
Buster?
Ash?
Ash, in here!
Buster?
I-I'm stuck!
You got to be kidding me.
Hold still.
What are you doing in there?
Ash, the show's off.
Crystal got mad
- and tried to kill me.
- What?
I thought you were his thugs
coming here to finish me off.
Oh, no. It's them.
Shh. Pretend we're not here.
The first time I leave home
in 15 years,
and what do I find?
The show is off, and this guy
is hiding in a suitcase.
No, no, don't...
don't open the door.
No, no, no.
Clay Calloway.
I remember you.
Miss Crawly.
- Pew, pew. Pew.
- Miss Crawly, wake up.
Wha... Mm, what?
Wake up.
We got to get out of here.
Coast is clear. Let's go.
Come on, Miss Crawly. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
We'll all feel better
when we're safe at home.
You sure about that?
'Cause I can tell you,
running and hiding away
is not all
that it's cracked up to be.
Well, we don't have a choice.
Yeah, well, all these years,
I thought the same,
but turns out
there's always a choice.
Just never had the guts
to make the right one.
Know what I mean?
Right? A victim.
I shut down my show
'cause of a talentless
little twerp called Buster Moon.
Seriously, you should've seen
this teeny, tiny loser.
Oh, and his pathetic
amateur friends...
let's just say,
whatever Podunk town
they crawled out of,
that's where they belong,
'cause it sure ain't
this great city.
No.
I see, Clay's right.
What we're trying to do here,
it takes guts.
Guys, wait.
We-we cannot let
that-that-that-that...
that bully steal
our hopes and dreams.
No, no, no. We are way past
singing and dancing now.
Look, I-I know
this might sound crazy.
- If we got the theater back...
- Oh, come on.
- Just for one night only.
- Seriously?
It's not like
we can just sneak in there
and put the show on
behind Crystal's back.
That is exactly
what we're gonna do.
Yes!
Maybe it's, like, room service?
Open up or you're dead, Moon!
Okay, it's not room service.
You and your dumb friends
better not be hiding in there.
What are we gonna do?
Guys, we just
got to be brave now.
Are you saying
we should fight these thugs?
No, no.
They'll beat us to a pulp.
We're gonna put this show on
whether Crystal likes it or not.
But first, we're gonna jump
out that window.
What?
I'm beginning to like this guy.
Security.
Yeah, we got nine suspects
loose on the river ride.
Repeat, nine suspects loose
on the river ride.
Hang on, everybody.
Uh, this is pool security.
I don't see anyone here. Over.
There!
They're heading east
through the back lot!
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, I wish I didn't have...
such teeny, tiny legs!
- ♪ Soy yo ♪
- ♪ Soy, soy, soy ♪
- ♪ Soy, soy, soy, soy ♪
- ♪ Soy yo ♪
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo... ♪
Thank you, Linda.
Thank you. Thanks, everybody.
Well?
Uh, no sign of 'em, sir.
We think they might
have split town.
No one is supposed
to be in here.
Uh, who are you?
We're the night cleaners.
Oh, I see.
Well, we don't need
any cleaning right now,
but it'd be better
if you didn't leave, so...
Mm, I don't suppose any of you
can tap-dance, huh?
Huh.
Well, let's move it, folks.
Here, Rosita.
It's your role.
Miss Crawly, let's see if we
can get us a new green alien.
Yes, sir, Mr. Moon, sir.
Rise and shine, sweetheart!
♪ Soy yo... ♪
Hey! You made it!
Yeah, well, uh, maybe
I overreacted a little before.
A little? You were, like,
a total drama queen back there.
Yeah, okay, we're all good now.
Wow, my dad's gonna flip
when he finds out about us.
- Well, we're safe for now, but listen, let's...
- Safe?
Uh, no.
None of us are safe.
Mr. Moon, I know someone
who can protect us.
Right. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah.
Protection?
Say no more, son.
We're on our way.
♪ Soy yo ♪
♪ Soy, soy, soy ♪
♪ Soy, soy, soy, soy ♪
- ♪ Soy yo ♪
- ♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo ♪
- ♪ Soy yo ♪
- ♪ Soy, soy, soy, soy ♪
Good night, Porsha.
♪ Soy yo. ♪
All right, be that way.
I don't care.
Spoiled little brat.
All right, time to get us
an audience.
Wait. Moon, as soon as you
start inviting folks in here,
hotel security will just
shut us down, right?
Oh, it's okay.
Rosita's got that covered.
Norman, release the piglets.
♪ No, not today... ♪
Hey, no!
All security, we have
a situation on floor 17.
Repeat, all security
to floor 17.
This is the best day
of my life, Daddy! Whoo!
Repeat, everybody to floor 17!
Wait, uh, is it on?
- Yes, it's on now.
- Oh, now?
- Yes, now.
- Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Before I blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah. Yeah, yeah, okay.
Good evening.
Uh, my name is Buster Moon,
and it is my great pleasure
to present to you,
for one night only
in the Crystal Tower Theater...
Mr. Crystal's office.
This is Jerry speaking.
a brand-new show
called Out of This World.
A musical space odyssey
featuring the return of
the legendary Clay Calloway.
That's right, Clay Calloway.
And what's more,
this show is completely free,
so step right up, folks,
and take your seats.
The journey of a lifetime
is about to begin.
All right, folks,
we all set back here?
There he is!
Dad.
- Come here.
- What are you wearing?
Oh, well, we're still doing
our community service,
ain't we, lads?
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Oh, my gosh. He's here.
Crystal's here?
No. M-My ice cream guy.
And he's sitting
in the front row.
- Mr. Crystal! Mr. Crystal!
- Aah! Jerry!
- Mr. Crystal, wake up, wake up.
- I tried to stop him, sir.
I-I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
to wake you up, sir.
It's Moon.
He's taken over the theater,
and he's putting on
a show right now.
He's what?!
Okay, this is it, guys.
You ready?
Oh, my gosh.
Are we really doing this?
Yeah, you better believe it.
Yeah, big-time, baby!
Remember...
There's only one way
left to go, and that's up!
- Yeah!
- Let's do it! Come on!
Gunter robot
activating piggy power.
Beep-beep, boop-boop.
Playback!
All creatures great and small,
welcome to outer space.
My name is Captain Rosita.
My mission: To find and rescue
a space explorer
who mysteriously
went missing long ago.
Captain, I am picking up
his signal.
Excellent.
But from which planet?
I see four of them ahead.
It is impossible
to know which one
the signal is, like,
coming from.
I see.
Then I'll have to
explore them all.
Take us down.
You've got this, big guy.
Remember what I said...
just go with the flow.
Mission report.
I must take care,
for I have landed
on the Planet of War.
♪ 'Cause you're a sky ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a sky
full of stars ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you my heart ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a sky ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a sky
full of stars ♪
♪ 'Cause you light up the path ♪
That's my boy.
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ Go on and tear me apart ♪
♪ I don't care if you do ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky
full of stars ♪
♪ I think I saw you... ♪
Yeah!
Give me that!
- And your costume. Now!
- Wait, what?
Take it off now!
Uh, we'll be at
the theater soon, sir.
I don't want to be there soon.
I want to be there now.
Yeah, we want to be there now.
Yes, sir.
♪ I don't care if you do ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky
full of stars ♪
♪ I think I saw you ♪
You see? You will never
be great, Johnny.
Oh, come on.
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ Go on and tear me apart ♪
♪ I don't care if you do ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky,
'cause in a sky ♪
- ♪ Full of stars ♪
- Yeah, that's more like it.
♪ I think I saw you! ♪
This is Barry. Come in. Over.
Yeah, go ahead, Barry.
Crystal's on site.
Repeat, Crystal is on site.
Over.
Roger that.
Right, let's go to work.
Mission report.
My search takes me
to the second planet,
the Planet of Joy.
All right. Here we go, Porsha.
Time to show the world
what you're really made of.
♪ Don't wanna live
as an untold story ♪
♪ Rather go out
in a blaze of glory ♪
♪ I can't hear you ♪
♪ I don't fear you ♪
♪ I'll live now
'cause the bad die last ♪
♪ Dodging bullets
with your broken past ♪
♪ Oh, I can't hear you ♪
♪ I don't fear you now ♪
♪ Wrapped in your regret... ♪
Hey, who the heck are you?
Where's my security?
We're security now, mate.
What?
♪ I wanna taste love and pain ♪
♪ Wanna feel pride and shame ♪
♪ I don't wanna take my time ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste one line ♪
♪ I wanna live better days ♪
♪ Never look back and say ♪
♪ It could've been me ♪
♪ It could've been me, yeah ♪
♪ Don't wanna wake up
on a Monday morning ♪
- Porsha!
- ♪ The thought of work's ♪
- ♪ Getting my skin crawling ♪
- Get off of there!
- ♪ I can't fear you ♪
- Don't you make me come out there!
♪ I don't hear you now ♪
♪ Wrapped in your regret ♪
♪ What a waste
of blood and sweat ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I wanna taste ♪
- ♪ Love and pain ♪
- ♪ I wanna taste love ♪
♪ Wanna feel pride and shame ♪
- ♪ I don't wanna take my time ♪
- ♪ No ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste
one line... ♪
You traitor.
That's it, I'm coming out there!
Miss Crawly put some cushions
and snacks down there,
so you should be comfortable
till the show's over.
You little...
♪ I wanna taste love and pain ♪
- ♪ Wanna feel pride and shame ♪
♪ I don't wanna take my time ♪
♪ I don't wanna waste my time,
don't wanna waste one line ♪
♪ Never look back and say ♪
♪ It could've been me ♪
♪ Oh, it could've been me ♪
♪ It could've been me. ♪
Mission report.
No sign here
of the missing space explorer.
I'm moving to the next planet.
- Ready, Gina?
- It's Meena.
- Wait, what is?
- Never mind.
Listen, find that feeling.
It is now or never.
Okay. I'm ready now.
♪ I say
a little prayer for you ♪
♪ The moment I wake up ♪
- ♪ Before I put on my makeup ♪
- ♪ Makeup ♪
♪ I say a little prayer
for you ♪
♪ While combing my hair now ♪
♪ And wondering
what to wear now ♪
♪ Wear now ♪
♪ I say a little prayer
for you ♪
- ♪ For you ♪
- ♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Forever, ever ♪
♪ You'll stay in my heart
and I will love you ♪
♪ Forever, ever ♪
♪ We never will part ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
♪ Together, together... ♪
Oh, Mr. Crystal, where are you?
I'm trapped somewhere
under the stage.
I'll find you, sir.
Mr. Crystal, I'm coming!
♪ I run for the bus, dear ♪
♪ While riding ♪
- ♪ I think of us, dear ♪
- ♪ Us, dear ♪
- ♪ I say a little, oh ♪
- ♪ Prayer for you ♪
- ♪ Oh, shawty ♪
- ♪ At work ♪
♪ I just take time ♪
♪ And all through
my coffee break time ♪
- ♪ Break time ♪
- ♪ I say a little ♪
♪ Prayer for you ♪
- ♪ Forever and ever ♪
- ♪ Forever ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I will love you ♪
- ♪ Ever ♪
- ♪ I say a prayer for you ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
- ♪ Together, together ♪
- ♪ Together, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Would only be heartbreak ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Only be heartbreak ♪
♪ For me. ♪
Yes!
I am gonna win
a ton of awards for this.
Hi.
Um, hi.
I'm Meena.
Oh. Um, Alfonso.
You-you were incredible.
So were you.
Um, what?
Oh. Uh, uh, never mind.
Um, want to meet up
after the show, maybe?
Uh, okay.
Okay, great. Bye.
Captain, we cannot land
on the last planet.
There is, like, a huge wormhole.
The ship will never make it.
You're right. It won't make it.
But I will.
♪ If you want it ♪
- ♪ Take it ♪
- ♪ Beep-beep, boop-boop ♪
♪ I should have said it before ♪
♪ Boop-boop-boop, beep ♪
♪ Tried to hide it ♪
- Watch your fingers.
- ♪ Fake it ♪
- ♪ I can't pretend anymore ♪
- ♪ Boop ♪
♪ I only want to die alive ♪
♪ Never by the hands
of a broken heart ♪
♪ Boop ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear you
lie tonight ♪
Rosita, you've got to jump.
Oh, honey.
Come on, Rosita.
- Look out!
- Whoa!
- Daddy, stop it!
- No!
- Mr. Moon!
- Mr. Crystal, no!
Well, I've got you now,
you lowlife little loser.
No, sir.
I'm not a loser.
We did what we came here to do.
And there is nothing
you can do or say
to change that.
Oh, I can do whatever I want.
♪ This is ♪
♪ The part when I say
I don't want ya ♪
♪ I'm stronger than I've been before ♪
♪ This is ♪
♪ The part when I break free ♪
Aah! Whoa...!
♪ 'Cause I can't
resist it no more ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa,
the thought of your body ♪
- ♪ I came alive ♪
- ♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ It was lethal, it was fatal ♪
♪ In my dreams,
it felt so right ♪
♪ But I woke up ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ This is ♪
♪ The part when I say
I don't want ya ♪
♪ I'm stronger than
I've been before ♪
♪ This is ♪
♪ The part when I break free ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't
resist it no more ♪
♪ Beep-beep, boop-boop. ♪
Woo-hoo!
I love you!
Yeah!
Oh, Mr. Moon, are you okay?
Yeah. Never better.
Uh, where's Ash and Clay?
Clay.
Clay, you back here?
We're on next.
You okay?
Uh-huh.
Mission report.
We have survived the wormhole.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
And arrived on the last planet.
The missing space explorer
must be here somewhere,
but there's no sign of life
on my scanner.
That's your cue.
Clay, it's time to go on.
But I see no signs of life.
Nothing but an empty cave.
- Clay.
- Oh, no.
It's okay. Just sing.
- Your songs will carry you.
- No.
- This is a mistake.
- Please.
It's been so long.
I'm not ready.
I'm sorry.
♪ I have climbed ♪
♪ The highest mountains ♪
♪ I have run ♪
♪ Through the fields ♪
♪ Only to be with you ♪
♪ But I still haven't found ♪
♪ What I'm looking for ♪
♪ I believe ♪
♪ In the kingdom come ♪
♪ Then all the colors ♪
♪ Will bleed into one ♪
♪ Bleed into one ♪
♪ But yes, I'm still running ♪
♪ You broke the bonds ♪
♪ And you loosed the chains ♪
♪ Carried the cross ♪
♪ Of my shame, of my shame ♪
♪ You know I believe it ♪
♪ But I still haven't found ♪
♪ What I'm looking for ♪
♪ I still haven't found ♪
♪ But I still haven't found ♪
♪ What I'm looking for ♪
Mission accomplished.
We're heading home.
♪ What I'm looking for. ♪
- Hey, Mr. Moon!
- Come on!
- Get out here, Moon.
- Come on out here!
Jimmy!
Oh, my gosh,
listen to that crowd.
You are a genius.
Yeah, you really are
a genius, sir.
Yeah, you got that right, Linda.
Thank you, thank you.
Too kind.
I appreciate it, really.
I-I do.
Look, I am very proud
of this show.
We did great work here.
Great work.
And my good friend, Clay...
great to have him back, right?
Yeah!
And listen, I look forward
to seeing this show run
at my theater
for many, many years to come.
Right, Moon?
Moon?
Officers, arrest that wolf.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
He's innocent!
Mr. Crystal, please!
I love you!
♪ Was a Monday morning ♪
♪ 'Bout a quarter past 4:00 ♪
♪ You were busy dreaming ♪
♪ So what did you wake up for? ♪
♪ Are you a stranger
in your own life? ♪
♪ What are you hiding
behind those eyes? ♪
♪ Is no one looking
for you there? ♪
♪ You know your song
saved my life ♪
♪ I don't sing it
just so I can get by ♪
♪ Won't you hear me ♪
♪ When I tell you, darlin' ♪
♪ I sing it to survive ♪
Stop the bus!
Whoa!
- What is it?
- What happened?
- What's going on?
- Ow!
I just got a call
from The Majestic.
They think your show
is fantastic,
and they want to put it on
at their theater.
Well, what do you say,
Mr. Calloway?
You in?
♪ Your song saved my life ♪
♪ The worst and the best days ♪
♪ Of my life ♪
♪ I was broken, now I'm open ♪
♪ Your love keeps me alive ♪
♪ It keeps me alive ♪
♪ Your song saved my life ♪
♪ The worst and the best days ♪
♪ Of my life ♪
♪ Your song saved my life ♪
♪ Song saved my,
song saved my. ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ There's nothing
♪ Oh, I've been shaking ♪
♪ I love it when you go crazy ♪
♪ You take all my inhibitions ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ You take me places
that tear up my reputation ♪
♪ Manipulate my decisions ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ There's nothing
♪ 'Cause if we lost our minds
and we took it way too far ♪
♪ I know we'd be all right,
I know we would be all right ♪
♪ If you were by my side
and we stumbled in the dark ♪
♪ I know we'd be all right,
I know we would be all right ♪
♪ 'Cause if we lost our minds
and we took it way too far ♪
♪ I know we'd be all right,
I know we would be all right ♪
♪ If you were by my side
and we stumbled in the dark ♪
♪ I know we'd be all right,
we would be all right ♪
♪ Oh, I've been shaking ♪
♪ I love it when you go crazy ♪
♪ You take all my inhibitions ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ You take me places
that tear up my reputation ♪
♪ Manipulate my decisions ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing ♪
♪ Holdin' me back ♪
♪ Oh, whoa ♪
♪ There's nothing
holdin' me back ♪
♪ I feel so free ♪
♪ When you're with me, baby ♪
♪ Baby, there's nothing ♪
♪ Holdin' me back. ♪
Oh!